{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","address":"14260 Gratiot Ave","zipcode":"48205","owner":"Falcon Holdings, LLC","licenseNumber":"035262","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"5/30/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000689E77F18BBE54C018B25517AA374540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43715","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","inspectionDate":"2018-10-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"7","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"7","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43715","inspectionDate":"10/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"43715","inspectionDate":"10/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"inspectionid":"43715","inspectionDate":"10/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"inspectionid":"43715","inspectionDate":"10/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"43715","inspectionDate":"10/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"HOT HOLDING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"43715","inspectionDate":"10/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"3-501.11","violationDescription":"Stored frozen FOODS shall be maintained frozen.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not frozen solid","subProblem":"","location":"FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain frozen."},{"inspectionid":"43715","inspectionDate":"10/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"43715","inspectionDate":"10/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"43715","inspectionDate":"10/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"43715","inspectionDate":"10/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned when contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean properly when contaminated."}]},{"inspectionid":"41810","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","inspectionDate":"2018-03-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41810","inspectionDate":"3/14/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"rodents","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the rodent droppings","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"inspectionid":"41810","inspectionDate":"3/14/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FRYER AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"41810","inspectionDate":"3/14/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"CASHIER/CHECKOUT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"41810","inspectionDate":"3/14/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"39886","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","inspectionDate":"2017-09-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"2","pfcount":"2","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"39886","inspectionDate":"9/7/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"6-302.11","violationDescription":"A supply of toilet tissue shall be available at each toilet.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Toilet paper","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"39886","inspectionDate":"9/7/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"FRYER AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"39886","inspectionDate":"9/7/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"39886","inspectionDate":"9/7/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"HOT HOLDING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"39886","inspectionDate":"9/7/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE CLOSET","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."}]},{"inspectionid":"38259","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","inspectionDate":"2017-03-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38259","inspectionDate":"3/1/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"38259","inspectionDate":"3/1/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned when contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean properly when contaminated."}]},{"inspectionid":"36388","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","inspectionDate":"2016-08-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36388","inspectionDate":"8/31/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1176","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #974","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1176"}}